https://www.hondapartsdeals.com/privacy.php

Home » Catalog » Privacy Notice
My Account  |  Cart Contents  |  Checkout
Honda Parts Categories
Honda AccessoriesHonda PartsHonda Maintenance PartsHonda Merchandise
Information
Shipping & Returns Order Tracking Privacy Notice Install Guides Contact UsPrintable Catalog Gift Voucher FAQ Honda LinksForums Site Map
Honda Accessory Finder
Use keywords to find the accessory you are looking for.Advanced SearchView All Items
Honda Parts Search
Find Honda parts quickly
What's New?
Illuminated Door Sill Trim$211.82
Link
Privacy Notice
HondaPartsDeals.com values the privacy of our customers. We do not sell any personal information to other companies. In keeping to the highest Web standards,
we would like to detail what information we use, and how we use it:CookiesIf you are a member, and log in to our website, our site uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you change Web pages. We may also use cookies to keep track of which
shopping cart belongs to you. We do not belong to any groups that track users across Web sites.Contact and Personal InformationWhen you register for an account, we require personal information (like name, email address, and mailing address). We require
this information so we can maintain billing records.We reserve the right to share a customers contact and personal information with individuals and/or entities for legitimate purposes only on receipt of a court order to disclose such information.
We would use this information only as necessary.If we do use mailing lists for advertising or promotional purposes, we will always have a clear mechanism for you to remove yourself from future mailings.We also require information for shipping and billing products.
If you have any questions about this
privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can
Please contact us.
Shopping Cart
0 items
Bestsellers
01.Touch Up Paint02.Automatic Transmission Fluid (ATF DW-1)03.Oil Filter & Drain Plug Gasket04.Power Steering Fluid05.Antifreeze/Coolant Type 206.Manual Transmission Fluid07.All-Season Floor Mats (Pilot)08.Crossbars for roof rails (EX Models) (Pilot)09.All-Season Floor Mats(2005-2008 Odyssey)10.All Season Floor Mats(Civic)
Honda Accessory Specials
Sno-Rake$25.99$22.99
Honda Accessory Reviews
It includes switch ??? or sold separately and installation m ..
Copyright © 2015 Honda Parts DealsWe are proud to offer Genuine Honda Parts and Honda Accessories.
